themehunk.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy - ThemeHunk WordPress Responsive Themes

This page helps you to know how themehunk.com value your privacy and how we use and protect your details.  
Please read these details below.

### What personal information do we collect from you?

When purchasing our product or registering on our site we ask you to fill your name, email address, your location, mailing address or other information to serve you best with your experience.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or open a Support Ticket, provide us with feedback on our products or services, or enter information on our site.

### How do we use your information.

We can use your collected information in the following way.  
– To provide you best product according to customer response.  
– To quickly processs your transaction  
– To get reviews for services and products.  
– To improve our product and quality of website.

### How do we protect your information?

Your personal information is stored on secured servers and networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.  
All financial transactions are processed through a payment gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

### Paypal

When you make payment to purchase our product, all your personal information and credit card details are provided to Paypal. And the information you provide to Paypal are protected under the terms of “Paypal’s privacy policy”.

### Third party disclosure

As a rule, Themehunk will not sell, trade or otherwise transfer any personal data about its users to third parties without explicit consent from the users.  
This does not include:  
• other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business (including lawyers and accountants) or serving our users.  
• authors whose products we sell.  
• business partners or prospective business partners, in operations such as sale, acquisition, merger of our assets.  
All those parties agree to keep this information confidential and to their treatment according to the laws and rules on personal data protection.  
We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.

### Third party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### How to contact us

If you have any query regarding this then you can contact us at info@themehunk.com
